[
    {
        "question" : "Which planet has the largest diameter in the Solar System?",
        "choice1" : "Jupiter",
        "choice2" : "Venus",
        "choice3" : "Neptune",
        "choice4" : "Mars",
        "answer" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What phenomenon allows us to see the surface of the Moon more clearly?",
        "choice1" : "Lunar Eclipse",
        "choice2" : "Solar Eclipse",
        "choice3" : "Lunar Orbit",
        "choice4" : "Axial Tilt of the Moon",
        "answer" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "The \"Great Red Spot\" is a feature of which planet?",
        "choice1" : "Mars",
        "choice2" : "Jupiter",
        "choice3" : "Saturn",
        "choice4" : "Uranus",
        "answer" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which star is the closest neighbor to the Solar System?",
        "choice1" : "Alpha Centauri A",
        "choice2" : "Proxima Centauri",
        "choice3" : "Sirius",
        "choice4" : "Vega",
        "answer" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which galaxy is most similar to the Milky Way in terms of galaxy type?",
        "choice1" : "Andromeda Galaxy",
        "choice2" : "Distant Galaxy",
        "choice3" : "Redshift Galaxy",
        "choice4" : "Large Magellanic Cloud",
        "answer" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the explosive event that occurs at the end of a star's life cycle called?",
        "choice1" : "Stellar Explosion",
        "choice2" : "Doomsday",
        "choice3" : "Formation of Black Hole",
        "choice4" : "Supernova",
        "answer" : 4
    },
    {
        "question" : "On which planet's surface can you find the \"Farthest man-made object from its surface\"?",
        "choice1" : "Mars",
        "choice2" : "Jupiter",
        "choice3" : "Saturn",
        "choice4" : "Uranus",
        "answer" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "How many dwarf planets are there in the Solar System?",
        "choice1" : "1",
        "choice2" : "3",
        "choice3" : "5",
        "choice4" : "7",
        "answer" : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "What concept is the \"Hawking Radiation\" associated with?",
        "choice1" : "Black Holes",
        "choice2" : "Sunspots",
        "choice3" : "Star Cluster",
        "choice4" : "Comets",
        "answer" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "In which constellation can you find the star cluster known as \"Pleiades\" or \"Seven Sisters\"?",
        "choice1" : "Ursa Major",
        "choice2" : "Taurus",
        "choice3" : "Orion",
        "choice4" : "Cancer",
        "answer" : 2
    }
]
